Guide to the Leonard Rosenman Papers MSS.212
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Film Scores and Parts
  - Keeper of the City, Cue 10 M 1: Strings, Undated (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Keeper of the City, Cue 10 M 1: Percussion, Undated (Box 3, Folder 53)
    Instrumentation: 4 Perc, Harp, Pno
    Description: Marked with marker
  - Keeper of the City, Cue 10 M 2: Winds, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Instrumentation: Picc, Fl, 2 Ob, Cl, Bs Cl, Bsn, CnBsn, 4 Hn, 3 Tpt, 3 Tbn, Tba
  - Keeper of the City, Cue 10 M 2: Strings, Undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Keeper of the City, Cue 10 M 2: Percussion, Undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Keeper of the City, Cue 10 M 3: Winds, Undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Instrumentation: Picc, Fl, Ob, Eng Hn, Cl, Bs Cl, Bsn, Cntrbsn, 4 Hn, 3 Tpt, 3 Tbn, Tuba
  - Keeper of the City, Cue 10 M 3: Percussion, Undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
    Instrumentation: Vib, Bs Dr, Timp, Sn Dr, Sus Cym, Harp, 3 Vocal, Synth
  - Keeper of the City, Cue 10 M 4: Winds, Undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Keeper of the City, Cue 10 M 4: Strings, Undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Keeper of the City, Cue 10 M 4: Percussion, Undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
    Instrumentation: Timp, Bs Dr, Harp, Synth
  - Keeper of the City, Cue 10 M 5: Winds, Undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
    Instrumentation: 2 Fl, Ob, Eng Hn, Cl, Cl/Bs Cl, Bsn, Cntrbsn, 4 Hn, 3 Tpt, 3 Tbn, Tuba
  - Keeper of the City, Cue 10 M 5: Strings, Undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Keeper of the City, Cue 10 M 5: Percussion, Undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
    Instrumentation: Vib, Timp, Sn Dr, Bs Dr, Cym, Harp, Synth
  - Rebel Without A Cause,Cue Main Title: Winds, Undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
    Instrumentation: 3 Fl, Ob I, 2 Ob II, Cl, 2 Bsn, 2 Alt Sax, 2 Ten Sax, Bari Sax, 3 Hn, 3 Tpt, 3 Tbn, Tuba
    Description: Marked with pencil; some taped; mostly photocopies
  - Rebel Without A Cause, Cue Main Title: Strings, Undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
    Instrumentation: 27 Vln, 12 Vla, 12 Cel, 8 Bs
  - Rebel Without A Cause, Cue Main Title: Percussion, Undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
    Instrumentation: 4 Perc, Harp, 2 Pno
    Description: Marked with pencil; some taped; some photocopies
  - Rebel Without A Cause, Cue 5-A: Winds, Undated (Box 4, Folder 16)
    Instrumentation: 3 Fl, Ob, Bari Ob, 2 Cl, Bs Cl, Bsn, Cntrbsn, Alt Sax, Ten Sax, 3 Hn, 3 Tpt, 3 Tbn, Tuba
    Description: Unmarked; some photocopies
  - Rebel Without A Cause, Cue 5-A: Strings, Undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Rebel Without A Cause, Cue 5-A: Percussion, Undated (Box 4, Folder 18)
    Instrumentation: 2 Perc, Pno I/Celeste, Pno II/Celeste
  - Rebel Without A Cause, Cue 5-B: Winds, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Instrumentation: Picc, 2 Fl, Ob, Eng Hn, 2 Cl, Bs Cl, 2 Bsn, 3 Hn, 3 Tpt, 3 Tbn, Tuba
  - Rebel Without A Cause, Cue 5-B: Strings, Undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Instrumentation: 28 Vln, 10 Vla, 12 Cel, 8 Bs
  - Rebel Without A Cause, Cue 5-B: Percussion, Undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Rebel Without A Cause, Cue 5-C: Winds, Undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Instrumentation: 2 Fl, Cl, Bs Cl, 2 Bsn, 3 Hn, 3 Tpt, 3 Tbn, Tuba
    Description: Unmarked;some edges chewed
  - Rebel Without A Cause, Cue 5-C: Strings, Undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
    Instrumentation: 28 Vln, 12 Vla, 12 Cel, 8 Bs
    Description: Unmarked; some edges chewed
  - Rebel Without A Cause, Cue 5-C: Percussion, Undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Rebel Without A Cause, Cue 5-D: Winds, Undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
    Instrumentation: Fl I, Fl II/Picc, Fl III, Ob, Eng Hn, 2 Cl, Bs Cl, Bsn, Cntrbsn, 3 Hn, 3 Tpt, 3 Tbn, Tuba
  - Rebel Without A Cause, Cue 5-D: Strings, Undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
    Instrumentation: 28 Vln, 11 vla, 11 Cel, 8 Bs
  - Rebel Without A Cause, Cue 5-D: Percussion, Undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Rebel Without A Cause, Cue R 16: Winds, Undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
    Instrumentation: 3 Fl, 2 Ob, 3 Cl, Bs Cl, Bsn, Cntrbsn, 3 Hn, 3 Tpt, 3 Tbn, Tuba
    Description: marked with pencil; some photocopies
  - Rebel Without A Cause, Cue R 16: Strings (Folder 1 of 2), Undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
    Instrumentation: 27 Vln
  - Rebel Without A Cause, Cue R 16: Strings (Folder 2 of 2), Undated (Box 5, Folder 12)
    Instrumentation: 12 Vla, 12 Cel, 8 Bs
  - Rebel Without A Cause, Cue R 16: Percussion, Undated (Box 5, Folder 13)
    Instrumentation: 2 Perc, Pno/Celeste, Novachord/Pno
    Description: Marked with pencil; some taped
  - Rebel Without A Cause: Scores (Folder 1 of 3), Undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
    Cues: Photocopied piano reduction of "Knife Fight," Main Title, Reel 1: Part 2, Reel 1: Part 3, and Reel 2: Part 1, Reel 2: Part 2, Reel 3: Part 1, Reel 4A, Reel 4A with Extension, Reel 4: Part 1, Reel 4: Part 1, Reel 15: Part 1, Reel 5A, Reel 5A, Reel 5B, Reel 5, Reel 5C, Reel 5D, Reel 5D
    Description: Heavily marked with red and blue crayon; some marked with "Ray"; some taped; some photocopies
    Production Numbers: 36722, 36712, 36743, 36744, 36745, 36771, 36746, 36747, 36748, 36749
  - Rebel Without A Cause: Scores (Folder 2 of 3), Undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
    Cues: Reel 6: Part 1, Reel 6: Part 2, Reel 6: Part 2A, Reel 6: Part 3, Reel 7A, Reel 7A and Reel 8A, Reel 7: Part 1, Reel 7: Part 2, Reel 7: Part 3 and Reel 8: Part 1, Reel 8: Part 2, Reel 8: Part 3, Reel 9: Part 1, Reel 9: Part 2, Reel 10A "I'll String Along with You," Reel 10: Part 1, Reel 10: Part 2, Reel 10: Part 3 "Five O'Clock Whistle"
    Description: Lightly marked with pencil and red and blue crayon; some marked with "Ray"; some photocopies
    Production Numbers: 36750, 36751, 36752, 36754, 36753, 36755, 36756, 36757, 36758, 36759, 36760, 36761, 36762, 36763
  - Rebel Without A Cause: Scores (Folder 3 of 3), Undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
    Cues: Reel 10: Part 4, Reel 11: Part 2, Reel 11: Part 3, Reel 11: Part 4, Reel 12: Part 1, Reel 12: Part 2, Reel 13: Part 1, Reel 13: Part 2, Reel 13: Part 3 and Reel 14: Part 1, Reel 16
    Description: Lightly marked with red and blue crayon, some marked with "Ray"; some photocopies
    Production Numbers: 36764, 36765, 36766, 36767, 36768, 36769, 36770
  - Rebel Without A Cause: Songs, Undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Description: "Song of the Moon," "Man in the Moon"; Unmarked
    Production Numbers: 36775
  - Rebel Without A Cause: Unidentifiable Parts, Undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
    Description: 2 parts, Cue 5-C; edges chewed
  - Rebel Without A Cause: Scores, undated (Box 17, Folder 3-6, Box 18, Folder 1-6)
- Series II: Concert Music
  - Chamber Music No. 1: Winds, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    Instrumentation: Fl, Cl, Bs Cl, Bsn, Hn, 2 Tpt, Tbn
    Description: in copyist's hand; marked with pencil
  - Chamber Music No. 1: Strings, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Instrumentation: Vln I, Cel, Bs
    Description: in copyist's hand; marked with pencil; bound with tape
  - Chamber Music No. 1: Percussion, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Instrumentation: 3 Perc, Harp, Pno/Celeste
  - Chamber Music No. 4 -- Double Bass Concerto: Onion Skins, undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
    Instrumentation: Solo Bs, Vln II, Vla, Cel, Bs, Quartet I: Vln I, Vln II, Quartet II: Vln I, Vln II, Vla, Cel, Quartet III Vln II, Vla, Cel, Quartet IV Vln I, Vln II, Vla, Cel
    Description: onion skin masters, in copyist's hand
  - Fanfare for Eight Trumpets: Score, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    Instrumentation: 8 Tpt
    Description: in composer's hand, pencil on manuscript
  - Lenny's Theme: Piano, Undated (Box 9, Folder 6)
    Description: Photocopy of a sketch in composer's hand; unmarked
  - Symphony No. 1, of Dinosaurs: Winds, undated (Box 9, Folder 7)
    Instrumentation: Picc, 2 Fl, 2 Ob, Eng Hn, 2 Cl, Bs Cl, Bsn, Cntr Bsn, 4 Hn, 4 Tpt, 4 Tbn, Tuba
    Description: unmarked
  - Symphony No. 1, of Dinosaurs: Strings, undated (Box 9, Folder 8)
    Instrumentation: 2 Vln I, 2 Vln II, 2 Vla, 2 Cel, 2 Bs
  - Symphony No. 1, of Dinsoaurs: Percussion, Undated (Box 9, Folder 9)
    Instrumentation: Timp, 3 Perc, Harp, Pno/Celesta
  - Ten Two Part Inventions - Invention #I: Piano, Undated (Box 9, Folder 10)
    Description: Sketched in composer's hand; sketched with ink; unmarked; missing the remaining nine inventions
  - Threnody on a Song of K.R.: Winds, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    Instrumentation: Picc, 2 Fl, 2 Ob, Eng Hn, 2 Cl, Bs Cl, Alto Sax, 2 Bsn, Cn Bsn, 4 Hn, 4 Tpt, 3 Tbn, 2 Tba
    Description: Some pencil markings; pages yellowing; Printed orchestral parts; taped
  - Threnody on a Song of K.R.: Strings (Folder 1 of 2), 1971 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    Instrumentation: 8 Vln I, 8 Vln II
    Description: Printed orchestral parts, tape; Some pencil markings, pages yellowing.
  - Threnody on a Song of K.R.: Strings (Folder 2 of 2), 1971 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    Instrumentation: 6 Vla, 6 Cel, 5 Bs
    Description: Some pencil markings, pages yellowing; Printed orchestral parts, taped
  - Threnody on a Song of K.R.: Percussion, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    Instrumentation: 3 Perc, 4 Perc 2, 3 Perc III, 2 Perc IV, 2 Perc V, 3 Perc VI, 4 Drums, Bs Gtr, Celesta, Harp, Pno
    Description: Printed orchestral parts, taped;Some pencil markings, pages yellowing.
  - Threnody on a Song of K.R.: Winds (onion skins), 1971 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    Instrumention: Picc, 2 Fl, 2 Ob, Eng Hn, 2 Cl, Bs Cl, Alto Sax, 2 Bsn, Cn Bsn, 4 Hn, 4 Tpt, 3 Tbn, Tba
    Description: Onion Skins
  - Threnody on a Song of K.R.: Strings (onion skins) (Box 10, Folder 4)
    Instrumentation: Vln I, Vln II, Vla, Cel, Bs
  - Threnody on a Song of K.R.: Percussion (onion skins), 1971 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    Instrumentation: Perc, Perc 2, Perc III, Perc IV, Perc V, Perc VI, 4 Drums, Bs Gtr, Celesta, Harp, Pno
  - Unidentified Concert Music, Undated (Box 10, Folder 6)
    Description: 1 page (onion skin) of a third movement for violin and orchestra sketched in pencil; 1 page of flute fingerings for extended technique on manuscript paper
  - Untitled Solo Piano Piece (onion skin), Undated (Box 10, Folder 7)
    Description: sketched with ink; onion skin; missing page one; measures cut out; some stains
- Oversize - Series I: Film Scores and Parts
  - Aftermath: Scores, Undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Cues: 1 M 1, 2 M 1, 2 M 2, 2 M 3, 3 M 1, 3 M 2, 3 M 4, 4 M 1, 4 M 2, 5 M 1, 6 M 1, 7 M 1, 8 M 1, 10 M 1, 10 M 3 (E.T.)
    Description: Sketched in composer's hand; sketched in pencil; unmarked
  - Aftermath: Scores, Undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Description: Duplicate of preceding score; bound with tape
  - The Color of Evening: Scores, Undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
    Cues: 1 M 1, 1 M 2, 2 M 2, 2 M 3, 2 M 4, 3 M 2 R, 4 M 3 R, 4 M 1 R, 5 M 1 R, 6 M 1 R, 6 M 2 R, 6 M 3/ 7 MOR, 7 M 1, 8 M 1, 8 M 2, 8 M 4, 9 M 1, 9 M 2, 9 M 3, 10 M 1, 10 M 2 R, 10 M 3
    Description: Sketched in composer's hand; sketched with pencil; manuscript paper; unmarked
  - The Color of Evening: Scores, Undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - East of Eden Score: Suite and Finale, undated (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Fantastic Voyage: Original Sketches for 3 cues, Undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
    Cues: "Pulmonary Artery," "The Chart" and "The Proteus
    Description: Manuscript paper; sketched with pencil; bound with tape
  - Jurij: Scores, Undated (Box 8, Folder 2)
    Cues: 1 M 1 (Remembrance), 1 M 6 (Sole), 1 M 6 A (Sole), 1 M 6 B (Sole), 1 M 6 C (Sole), 1 M 8 (Father Remembers Estzer), 1 M 9 A (Father Remembers Estzer), 2 M 4 (Jurij Leaves The Train), 2 M 5 (Touching), 3 M 1 (Jurij Takes A Drink), 3 M 1 A (Jurij Hears The Rain), 3 M 3 (Isabella Studies Jurij), 3 M 5 (The Wind), 3 M 6 (Storm and Death), 4 M 5 (The Countryside), 4 M 5 A (A Hike To The Tree), 5 M 3 (The Abduction (Part 1)), 5 M 3 (The Abduction (Part 1-alt. end)), 5 M 4 (The Abduction (Part 2)), 5 M 5 (Finale); Includes score for Violin Ciacona; Includes Jurij Theme (Lea's Song)
    Description: pencil markings; some red pen; Michael Patterson's original orchestrations in his hand; Large score; sections bound with tape.
  - Keeper of the City: Scores, Undated (Box 8, Folder 3)
    Cues: 1 M 1, 1 M 1 A, 1 M 2, 2 M 2, 3 M 1, 3 M 3, 3 M 4, 4 M 1 B, 5 M 1, 6 M 2, 7 M M 1, 8 M 1, 8 M 2, 8 M 4, 9 M 1, 9 M 2, 10 M 1, 10 M 3, 10 M 4, 10 M 5
    Description: Manuscript paper; sketched in pencil; marked with red pencil; some tape
  - Mind Game: Scores, Undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
    Cues: 1 M 1, 1 M 2, 2 M 1, 2 M 2, 3 M 1, 3 M 2, 3 M 3, 4 M 1, 4 M 2, 4 M 4, 5 M 1, 5 M 2, 6 M 1, 6 M 2, 7 M 1, 7 M 3, 7 M 4, 8 M 1, 8 M 2, 8 M 3, 8 M 4, 9 M 1, 9 M 3, 9 M 4
    Description: Manuscript paper; sketched in pencil; marked in red pencil; bound by tape
  - Rebel Without a Cause Score: Suite, undated (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Unidentified Film Score, Undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
    Cues: 1 M 1, 1 M 2, 1 M 4, 1 M 5, 1 M 6, 1 M 7, 2 M 1, 2 M 2, 2 M 3, 2 M 4, 2 M 5, 3 M 1, 3 M 2, 4 M 2, 4 M 3, 4 M 5, 5 M 1, 5 M 3
    Description: Manuscript paper; sketched in pencil, marked with pencil
  - Unidentified Film Score, Undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
    Cues: 1 M 1, 1 M 2, 1 M 3, 2 M 3, 2 M 4, 2 M 5, 3 M 1, 3 M 2, 4 M 1, 4 M 2, 4 M 3, 4 M 4, 4 M 5, 5 M 1, 5 M 2, 5 M 4
    Description: Duplicate of preceding score; manuscript paper, sketched with pencil; bound with tape
  - Unidentified Film Score, Undated (Box 8, Folder 7)
    Description: Manuscript paper; sketched in composer's hand; sketched in pencil; 5 pages; possibly multiple cues; "Scene #49" at the top of one page
- Oversize - Series II: Concert Music
  - Chamber Music No. 1: Score, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    Description: Unmarked; pencil on manuscript paper
  - Chamber Music No. 1: Score (onion skins), 1960 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    Description: onion skins; unmarked
  - Chamber Music No. 1: Score, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    Description: Printed and bound duplicate of preceding score; unmarked
  - Chamber Music No. 3: Strings, undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
    Instrumentation: Vln I, Vln II, Solo Vla, Cel, Bs
    Description: Onion skins; unmarked
  - Chamber Music No. 4 (Double Bass Concerto): Score (onion skins), 1976 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    Description: onion skins sketched with pencil; unmarked
  - Chamber Music No. 4 (Double Bass Concerto): Score, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Chamber Music No. 4 (Double Bass Concerto): Score (onion skins), 1976 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    Description: onion skins sketched in ink; unmarked
  - Chamber Music No. 5: Winds (onion skins), 1979 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    Instrumentation: Fl, Cl
    Description: onion skins sketched with ink, unmarked
  - Chamber Music No. 5: Strings (onion skins), 1979 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    Instrumentation: Vln, Cel
    Description: onion skins sketched with ink; unmarked
  - Chamber Music No. 5: Percussion (onion skins), 1979 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    Instrumentation: Perc I, Perc II, Pno
  - Chamber Music No. 5: Score (onion skins), 1979 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    Description: onion skin sketched with ink; unmarked
  - Chamber Music No. 5: Score (onion skins), 1979 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    Desciption: onion skins sketched with pencil; unmarked
  - Concerto for Violin and Orchestra: Piano Reduction (onion skins), 1952 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Concerto for Violin and Orchestra: Score(onion skins), 1952 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Concerto for Violin and Orchestra: Violin (onion skins), 1952 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Double Concerto for Oboe and Clarinet: Score, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    Description: pencil on manuscript paper, in composer's hand; unmarked
  - Double Concerto for Oboe and Clarinet: Score, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    Description: Printed, bound duplicate of preceding score; unmarked
  - Duo for Clarinet and Piano (onion skins), 1961 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    Instrumentation: Cl, Pno
  - Duo for Violin and Piano (onion skins), 1970 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    Instrumentation: Vln, Pno
  - Foci I: Winds (onion skins), 1981 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    Instrumentation: Fl/Picc, Fl II, Ob I, Ob/Eng Hn, Cl I, Cl/Bs Cl, Bsn I, Bsn/Cntr Bsn, 2 Hn, 2 Tpt, Tbn
  - Foci I: Winds (onion skins), 1981 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    Description: onion skin duplicates of preceding parts; unmarked
  - Foci I: Strings (onion skins) (Folder 1 of 2), 1981 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    Instrumentation: 16 Vln
  - Foci I: Strings (onion skins) (Folder 2 of 2), 1981 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    Instrumentation: 5 Vln, 2 Vla, 2 Cel, 2 Bs
  - Foci I: Percussion (onion skins), 1981 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Foci I: Percussion (onion skins), 1981 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    Description: onion skin duplicate of preceding part; unmarked
  - Foci I: Score (onion skins), 1981 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Foci I: Score, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    Description: Printed and bound duplicate of preceding onion skins; unmarked
  - Piano Sonata (onion skins), 1949 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Prelude and Four Scenes: Score, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    Description: pencil on manuscript paper; unmarked
  - Six Songs on Texts of Lorca: Piano Score (onion skins), 1950-1952 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - When Alpha Met Beta (String Quartet): Score, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Themes and Elaborations: Piano (onion skin), 1951 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Time Travel: Hugo Wolf to Song at Sunset: Score, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    Description: Handwritten Conductor's score; manuscript paper; sketched with pencil; unbound
  - Unidentified Concert Music, Undated (Box 15, Folder 2)
    Description: 1 page of piano score for solo instrument and piano; 2 pages of score for solo instrument and orchestra; 1 page of percussion listing; 1 page (pg 166) of a score from a solo for Violin and orchestra; 1 page of a score from a soprano and chamber piece, second movement title reads: "Moquerie"
  - Unidentified Concert Music: Score [Jurij, Symphony No. 1, or A Walk in N.Y.], Undated (Box 15, Folder 3)
    Description: Sketch in composer's hand; sketeched with pencil; manuscript paper; 23 pages; could possibly be Jurij, Symphony No. 1: Of Dinosaurs, or A Walk in New York
  - Unidentified Concert Music: Score [Jurij, Violin Concerto, or A Walk in N.Y.], Undated (Box 15, Folder 4)
    Description: Sketch in composer's hand; sketched with pencil; manuscript paper; 22 pages; could be Jurij, Violin Concerto, or A Walk in New York
  - Unidentified Concert Music: Score [Symphony No. 1, or A Walk in N.Y.], Undated (Box 15, Folder 5)
    Description: Sketched in composer's hand; sketched with pencil; manuscript paper; 16 pages; could be Symphony No. 1: of Dinosaurs, or A Walk in New York
  - Untitled Solo Instrument Piece, Undated (Box 15, Folder 6)
    Description: Sketched in composer's hand; sketched with pencil; manuscript paper; piano score; solo instrument is in the bass clef
  - Untitled Solo Piano Piece (onion skins), Undated (Box 15, Folder 7)
    Description: Sketched with ink; onion skin; 25 pages; solo piano
  - Violin Concerto II: Score, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Violin Concerto II: Score (rewrite), 1994 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    Description: Sketched in composer's hand; sketched with pencil; rewrite of 1991 Violin Concerto II; unmarked
  - Foci I: Score (onion skin), 1981 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    Description: onion skin; printed with ink; unmarked; some pages torn
  - Symphony No. 1, of Dinosaurs: Score, Undated (Box 16, Folder 2)
    Description: Sketched in composer's hand; sketched with pencil; unmarked; manuscript paper; 147 pages
  - Symphony No. 1, of Dinosaurs: Score (rewrite), Undated (Box 16, Folder 3)
    Description: Duplicate of preceding score; Sketched in composer's hand; sketched with pencil; unmarked; rewrite of original; 35 pages; missing many pages
  - A Walk in New York: Score, Undated (Box 16, Folder 4)
    Description: Sketched in composer's hand; sketched with pencil; unmarked; pages 1, 2, 3, 8, and 9 only; some pages duplicated; manuscript paper
  - Threnody on a Song of K.R., 1971 (Box 16, Folder 7)